Cardboard Man<BR>
Tim Watson<BR>
<BR>
I see him in the grocery store; he&#039;s been there quite a while.<BR>
Stands by the coke machine, and always has a smile.<BR>
People walk right past him with their cartons and their cans.<BR>
On one side he says Welcome, and on the other Come Again.<BR>
<BR>
He&#039;s just a piece of cardboard, but I like him just the same.<BR>
Doesn&#039;t try to judge me; he&#039;s just happy that I came.<BR>
He sees my frozen pizza, my coffee and my beer.<BR>
He watches me go rolling through the produce and the years.<BR>
<BR>
Chorus - And I say hey, to the cardboard man.<BR>
Just one dimension, and needin&#039; some attention,<BR> 
he&#039;s doin&#039; the best he can<BR>
I say hey to the cardboard man.<BR>
Cause me and you, sometimes we&#039;re cardboard too<BR>
So say hey to the cardboard man.<BR>
<BR>
I&#039;ve seen him lose his balance; I&#039;ve seen him hit the floor<BR>
Someone always comes along and props him up for more.<BR>
I&#039;ve seen him face the wrong direction, when he gets turned around<BR>
He ends up stranded in a corner and he never makes a sound.<BR>
<BR>
Sometimes I wish that he could talk.  I wonder what he&#039;d say.<BR>
I reckon he&#039;d just smile at me and then he&#039;d turn away.<BR>
Cause there ain&#039;t no use in telling me what I already know -<BR>
It ain&#039;t so hard to stand in place, <BR>
cause when you&#039;re only one dimension, you&#039;ve got no place to go.<BR>
<BR>
Chorus<BR>
<BR>
There&#039;s cardboard people everywhere; they&#039;re tattered and they&#039;re torn<BR>
Living lives of cardboard from the day that they were born.<BR>
But most of them will be OK with just a little help.<BR>
You can feel free to start with me, I&#039;m feelin&#039; kinda flat myself.<BR>
<BR>
Chorus<BR>
<BR>
Cause me and you, we could be cardboard, too,<BR>
But for the hand of fate it could be me and you, so always,<BR> 
please, take the time to say hey to the Cardboard Man.<BR>
He&#039;s just a cardboard man.<BR>

