One Face at a Time<BR>
Tim Watson<BR>
<BR>
Rita went to law school with a lifetime of dreams<BR>
Waiting on her graduation day.<BR>
She was staring straight ahead, but there was something that she&#039;d seen<BR>
Caught her eye, made her look away.<BR>
<BR>
The faces of people she&#039;d see now and then<BR>
Changed all the plans she&#039;d made.<BR>
Faces on the outside, always peering in<BR>
And Rita said “I think I&#039;ll work a year, maybe two, in legal aid.”<BR>
<BR>
She serves the blind-folded lady who&#039;s holding justice in her hands<BR>
And Rita thinks that everyone should try to make a difference when they can.<BR>
<BR>
She goes the extra mile, one case at a time,<BR>
Gives the world a smile, one face at a time,<BR>
Other plans can wait for other days;<BR>
She&#039;s got work to do in legal aid.<BR>
<BR>
Time goes rolling by and she&#039;s making a difference<BR>
In the faces that she sees<BR>
And Rita&#039;s face is changing too; ‘cause now she sees clearly<BR>
The world the way it ought to be.<BR>
<BR>
She doesn&#039;t make much money like she did in all her dreams<BR>
But she doesn&#039;t really mind<BR>
She knows down in her soul that the dream she&#039;s living in<BR>
Is better than the one she left behind.<BR>
<BR>
And Rita sometimes loses, but she never really fails,<BR>
Cause the blind-folded lady knows she&#039;s always standing there by the scales.<BR>
<BR>
She goes the extra mile one case at a time, <BR>
Gives the world a smile, one face at a time,<BR>
Those other plans have all begun to fade<BR>
She&#039;s got work to do; those faces keep on coming through<BR>
She&#039;ll work another year, maybe two, in legal aid.<BR>
<BR>
Rita went to law school with a thousand people&#039;s dreams<BR>
Waiting on her graduation day.<BR>
