They Look A Lot Like Me (Gettysburg)<BR>
Tim Watson<BR>
<BR>
Blue summer&#039;s day in 1863<BR>
The men in gray are coming through the trees<BR>
And even at this distance I can clearly see<BR>
These boys that we call rebel devils look a lot like me<BR>
<BR>
Blue summer sky stretches overhead<BR>
Third of July, turning red<BR>
They&#039;re coming into range, stretch out on the ground<BR>
Stare down that long, long barrel; another one goes down<BR>
<BR>
Blue summer&#039;s day, rise and look around<BR>
Red, blue, and gray twisted on the ground<BR>
They&#039;re staring at each other with eyes that do not see<BR>
And I can&#039;t help but wonder how much more of this there&#039;ll be<BR>
Cause they all look a lot like me<BR>
Repeat and fade<BR>

