Jesus in the Kitchen<BR>
Tim Watson<BR>
<BR>
I spilled some chocolate syrup on my kitchen floor<BR>
A lamentable condition that I chose to ignore<BR>
It got smeared around a bit for all the world to see<BR>
Cleanliness is never a priority for me.<BR>
<BR>
My fundamental neighbor came to talk about my soul.<BR>
He talked about damnation while he ate a jelly role.<BR>
He dropped a little jelly on the stain already there<BR>
He said “It looks just like a face,” and then I got a scare<BR>
<BR>
Cause he yelled “Hallelujah, you&#039;ve got Jesus in the kitchen.”<BR>
He danced around his chair and he kept on pointing to the floor<BR>
Screaming “Glory Hallelujah, you&#039;ve got Jesus in the kitchen.”<BR>
He started quoting verses, and he shot right out the door.<BR>
<BR>
Now there&#039;s a painting of the Savior in my Holy Book.<BR>
I tried to keep an open mind and I gave it a look.<BR>
I looked back at the floor for any similarity,<BR>
But it just looked like jelly and some chocolate to me.<BR>
<BR>
But a crowd began to gather out in my front yard<BR>
Some were toting signs and some were sitting on my car<BR>
My bible-quoting neighbor was amongst ‘em, yellin&#039; loud<BR>
I walked up to the porch rail, and I addressed the crowd.<BR>
<BR>
And I said “I&#039;m glad y&#039;all&#039;ve got religion; it&#039;s my religion, too.<BR>
But there&#039;s nothing here to see; and I wouldn&#039;t lie to you.<BR>
It ain&#039;t the face of Jesus, and I&#039;ll tell you one thing more:<BR>
When Jesus comes again it won&#039;t be on my kitchen floor.”<BR>
<BR>
But they screamed “Hallelujah, you&#039;ve got Jesus in the kitchen.”<BR>
The mob began to grumble; they were getting kinda wild.<BR>
Yelling “Glory Hallelujah, you&#039;ve got Jesus in the kitchen.”<BR>
They were holdin&#039; rakes and kissin&#039; snakes and I thought I might die.<BR>
<BR>
But then a man approached me with a camera in his hand.<BR>
He was from the biggest tabloid rag in all the land.<BR>
He said he&#039;d pay a thousand bucks to get a photograph<BR>
Of the stain that looked like Jesus, and I let go a laugh<BR>
<BR>
And I yelled, “Hallelujah, I&#039;ve got Jesus in the kitchen.<BR>
Everyone can come on in and see my kitchen floor.”<BR>
And they all looked and said “This ain&#039;t no Jesus in your kitchen.”<BR>
They grabbed my little neighbor and they headed for the door.<BR>
And he was callin&#039; out for Jesus as they dragged him out the door.<BR>

