A Light up in the Sky<BR>
by Tim Watson<BR>
<BR>
There&#039;s a light up in the sky<BR>
There&#039;s a light up in the sky<BR>
We&#039;re all lookin&#039; up and wonderin&#039; why<BR>
There&#039;s a light up in the sky<BR>
<BR>
They came from far away<BR>
So very far away<BR>
Some people say they might be here to stay<BR>
They came from far away<BR>
<BR>
Wonder what they&#039;re doin&#039; here and if they look like us<BR>
What are their intentions? Are they honest, are they just?<BR>
Will we be their servants, will we be their friends”<BR>
Will they show us wonders, or tell us it&#039;s the end?<BR>
<BR>
This could be a blessing or a curse<BR>
This could be a blessing or a curse<BR>
Things just might get better, but they could get a whole lot worse<BR>
This could be a blessing or a curse<BR>

They say we live in darkness and they&#039;re bringing us the light<BR>
And we don&#039;t know enough to know if that&#039;s wrong or right<BR>
We&#039;ve got our suspicions and we&#039;re reaching for our guns<BR>
But we should be real careful ‘cause there ain&#039;t no place to run<BR>
<BR>
There&#039;s a light up in the sky<BR>
There&#039;s a light up in the sky<BR>
Don&#039;t know if we should laugh or we should cry<BR>
Jump for joy or just lay down and die<BR>
We&#039;re all lookin&#039; up and we&#039;re wonderin&#039; why<BR>
There&#039;s a light up in the sky<BR>
<BR>
Repeat and fade
