Switching Sides<BR>
Tim Watson<BR>
<BR>
I see women holding hands with other women<BR>
Arms around each other as they stroll<BR>
And here I am a man who just can&#039;t understand<BR>
Why I can&#039;t get a girl to have and hold<BR>
<BR>
I&#039;ve been trying all my life to get a woman<BR>
But I&#039;ve only met with limited success<BR>
When they go out with me somehow they come to see<BR>
That they like women more and fellows less<BR>
<BR>
So I watch women holding women that I could never get<BR>
But it&#039;s not completely hopeless.  No, I&#039;m no beaten yet<BR>
I see the way to women now, and I&#039;m gonna get me one<BR>
I&#039;m gonna get me a sex change, so I can be a lesbian<BR>
Lesbian, lesbian – I&#039;m gonna be a lesbian<BR>
Yeah I&#039;m gonna get me a sex change and then I can be lesbian<BR>
<BR>
Now some will say that what I plan is cheating<BR>
And I confess I&#039;m feeling kinda sly,<BR>
It&#039;s gender slight-of-hand; inside I&#039;ll stay a man<BR>
While everyone will think I&#039;m switching sides.<BR>
<BR>
The more I think about it, the more I understand<BR>
My destiny has only just begun<BR>
I&#039;ll still be in the game; the target&#039;s just the same<BR>
It&#039;s only that I&#039;m giving up my gun<BR>
<BR>
These women holding women that I could never get<BR>
They&#039;ll soon have competition, cause I&#039;ve got one trick yet<BR>
I see the way to women now, and I&#039;m gonna get me one <BR>
I&#039;m gonna get me a sex change, and I can be a lesbian<BR>
Lesbian, lesbian – I&#039;m gonna be a lesbian<BR>
Yeah I&#039;m gonna get me a sex change and I can be lesbian<BR>
<BR>
And when the doctor&#039;s done, then all the world can see<BR>
How this hard and lonely life has made a woman out of me<BR>
These women loving women, they&#039;ve been having all the fun<BR>
So I&#039;m gonna get me a sex change, and I can be a lesbian<BR>
Lesbian, lesbian – I&#039;m gonna be a lesbian<BR>
Yeah I&#039;m gonna get me a sex change and I can be a les-bi-an<BR>
