Silver Wings (Fly All Night)<BR>
by Tim Watson<BR>
<BR>
Staring out a little window, the ground below me drops away<BR>
There&#039;s a couple holding hands beside me, it takes me back to better days<BR>
<BR>
When you and I were less than married, but something so much more than friends<BR>
I&#039;m countin&#039; on these silver wings, to take me back to you again<BR>
<BR>
Chorus<BR>
Silver wings, fly all night<BR>
Set me down in morning light<BR>
She&#039;s waiting there for me<BR>
Silver Wings.<BR>
<BR>
Second Verse<BR>
I&#039;m not a friend of second chances. They never seem to come my way.<BR>
But maybe my fortune&#039;s changing; I got your message yesterday<BR>
<BR>
And you don&#039;t know if we can make it, but you&#039;re thinkin&#039; maybe we should try<BR>
I&#039;m on my way to you tonight, on this road up in the sky<BR>
<BR>
Chorus<BR>
Silver wings, fly all night<BR>
Set me down in morning light<BR>
She&#039;s waiting there for me<BR>
Silver Wings.<BR>
<BR>
Bridge<BR>
I feel like I&#039;m in the hands of something I can&#039;t see<BR>
But if it gets me back to you, then that&#039;s all right with me.<BR>
<BR>
Third Verse<BR>
It seems to me the sky is brighter.  But maybe it&#039;s just in my mind.<BR>
I&#039;ve been looking forward for so long, to leaving all these years behind.<BR>
<BR>
Chorus<BR>
Silver wings, fly all night<BR>
Set me down in morning light<BR>
You can leave the rest to me.<BR>
Silver Wings.<BR>
Silver Wings.<BR>
