God Bless Chuck Darwin<BR>
Tim Watson<BR>
<BR>
In the 1800&#039;s a good man walked the earth<BR>
Chuck Darwin was his name, and he was the first<BR>
To understand clearly the order of life<BR>
But his book led to decades of strife<BR>
Decades of anger and decades of strife<BR>
<BR>
A hundred years later they found DNA<BR>
In all of God&#039;s creatures.  It showed the way<BR>
That we are related to all living things<BR>
Walkers and swimmers and things that have wings<BR>
Crawlers and sliders and all living things<BR>
<BR>
Stop wearing blinders and saying there&#039;s a schism<BR>
Between God and Darwin, cause there really isn&#039;t<BR>
Chuck was flesh and blood, with kids and a wife<BR>
And he could see so clearly the wonder of life.<BR>
<BR>
In the Good Book, a verse can be found<BR>
It says we were made from the dust of the ground<BR>
I don&#039;t think old Darwin disagreed with that line<BR>
He only thought it took a long time<BR>
Creation of humankind took a long time<BR>
<BR>
Still so many people, just won&#039;t believe.<BR>
There are none so blind as those who won&#039;t see<BR>
How the truth of his teachings set us all free.<BR>
“Bang, you are created” just didn&#039;t work for me<BR>
That old-timey version just wasn&#039;t for me.<BR>
<BR>
So stop wearing blinders and saying there&#039;s a schism<BR>
Between God and Darwin cause you know there isn&#039;t<BR>
Chuck was a good man who told us the truth.<BR>
God bless us all, and Chuck Darwin, too<BR>
God bless us every single one… and Chuck Darwin, too<BR>

