Makin&#039; This CD<BR>
By Tim Watson<BR>
<BR>
First Verse<BR>
<BR>
Oh I lay awake this mornin&#039; wishin&#039; I could just stay there in bed<BR>
Cause I knew that I&#039;d end up this way, in this situation that I dread<BR>
<BR>
These double microphones are starin&#039; like a pair of eyes<BR>
And I&#039;m about to play a song I wrote and I despise<BR>
I&#039;m croakin&#039; like a frog and countin&#039; one, two, three.<BR>
Makin&#039; this CD is killin&#039; me.<BR>
<BR>
Second Verse<BR>
<BR>
I ain&#039;t lookin&#039; to be famous; I just thought it might be kinda fun<BR>
But I&#039;m caught up in a vortex, ain&#039;t no place to hide, no place to run<BR>
<BR>
I&#039;ve been spendin&#039; money that I&#039;ll never see again<BR>
I think my health is failing in a fight that I can&#039;t win<BR>
And even as the world grows darker I can finally see<BR>
that makin&#039; this CD is killin&#039; me.<BR>
<BR>
Third Verse<BR>
<BR>
It&#039;s a world gone crazy, ‘n&#039; I&#039;ve still got some friends I&#039;d like to get to<BR>
But the only ones that I see around me – they&#039;re the friends I write the checks to<BR>
<BR>
I guess no one will ever really know the price I&#039;ve paid<BR>
I&#039;ll just keep on keepin&#039; on until that final day <BR>
Just three little things keep on getting&#039; in the way – <BR>
I can&#039;t write, I can&#039;t sing, and I can&#039;t play.<BR>
<BR>
Fourth verse<BR>
<BR>
First two lines instrumental<BR>
<BR>
I&#039;d like to breathe some fresher air; I&#039;d like to see the sky<BR>
My knees are weak and shakin&#039;, and my mouth is feelin&#039; dry<BR>
I&#039;m stuck here in this vocal booth and I really need to pee…<BR>
Makin&#039; this CD is killin&#039; me.<BR>

Makin&#039; this CD is really thrillin&#039;… but it&#039;s really killin&#039; me.<BR>
