Cardboard Man
Tim Watson

I see him in the grocery store; he's been there quite a while.
Stands by the coke machine, and always has a smile.
People walk right past him with their cartons and their cans.
On one side he says Welcome, and on the other Come Again.

He's just a piece of cardboard, but I like him just the same.
Doesn't try to judge me; he's just happy that I came.
He sees my frozen pizza, my coffee and my beer.
He watches me go rolling through the produce and the years.

Chorus - And I say hey, to the cardboard man.
Just one dimension, and needin' some attention, 
he's doin' the best he can
I say hey to the cardboard man.
Cause me and you, sometimes we're cardboard too
So say hey to the cardboard man.

I've seen him lose his balance; I've seen him hit the floor
Someone always comes along and props him up for more.
I've seen him face the wrong direction, when he gets turned around
He ends up stranded in a corner and he never makes a sound.

Sometimes I wish that he could talk.  I wonder what he'd say.
I reckon he'd just smile at me and then he'd turn away.
Cause there ain't no use in telling me what I already know -
It ain't so hard to stand in place, 
cause when you're only one dimension, you've got no place to go.

Chorus

There's cardboard people everywhere; they're tattered and they're torn
Living lives of cardboard from the day that they were born.
But most of them will be OK with just a little help.
You can feel free to start with me, I'm feelin' kinda flat myself.

Chorus

Cause me and you, we could be cardboard, too,
But for the hand of fate it could be me and you, so always, 
please, take the time to say hey to the Cardboard Man.
He's just a cardboard man.

