One Face at a Time
Tim Watson

Rita went to law school with a lifetime of dreams
Waiting on her graduation day.
She was staring straight ahead, but there was something that she'd seen
Caught her eye, made her look away.

The faces of people she'd see now and then
Changed all the plans she'd made.
Faces on the outside, always peering in
And Rita said “I think I'll work a year, maybe two, in legal aid.”

She serves the blind-folded lady who's holding justice in her hands
And Rita thinks that everyone should try to make a difference when they can.

She goes the extra mile, one case at a time,
Gives the world a smile, one face at a time,
Other plans can wait for other days;
She's got work to do in legal aid.

Time goes rolling by and she's making a difference
In the faces that she sees
And Rita's face is changing too; ‘cause now she sees clearly
The world the way it ought to be.

She doesn't make much money like she did in all her dreams
But she doesn't really mind
She knows down in her soul that the dream she's living in
Is better than the one she left behind.

And Rita sometimes loses, but she never really fails,
Cause the blind-folded lady knows she's always standing there by the scales.

She goes the extra mile one case at a time, 
Gives the world a smile, one face at a time,
Those other plans have all begun to fade
She's got work to do; those faces keep on coming through
She'll work another year, maybe two, in legal aid.

Rita went to law school with a thousand people's dreams
Waiting on her graduation day.
