They Look A Lot Like Me (Gettysburg)
Tim Watson

Blue summer's day in 1863
The men in gray are coming through the trees
And even at this distance I can clearly see
These boys that we call rebel devils look a lot like me

Blue summer sky stretches overhead
Third of July, turning red
They're coming into range, stretch out on the ground
Stare down that long, long barrel; another one goes down

Blue summer's day, rise and look around
Red, blue, and gray twisted on the ground
They're staring at each other with eyes that do not see
And I can't help but wonder how much more of this there'll be
Cause they all look a lot like me
Repeat and fade

