Jesus in the Kitchen
Tim Watson

I spilled some chocolate syrup on my kitchen floor
A lamentable condition that I chose to ignore
It got smeared around a bit for all the world to see
Cleanliness is never a priority for me.

My fundamental neighbor came to talk about my soul.
He talked about damnation while he ate a jelly role.
He dropped a little jelly on the stain already there
He said “It looks just like a face,” and then I got a scare

Cause he yelled “Hallelujah, you've got Jesus in the kitchen.”
He danced around his chair and he kept on pointing to the floor
Screaming “Glory Hallelujah, you've got Jesus in the kitchen.”
He started quoting verses, and he shot right out the door.

Now there's a painting of the Savior in my Holy Book.
I tried to keep an open mind and I gave it a look.
I looked back at the floor for any similarity,
But it just looked like jelly and some chocolate to me.

But a crowd began to gather out in my front yard
Some were toting signs and some were sitting on my car
My bible-quoting neighbor was amongst ‘em, yellin' loud
I walked up to the porch rail, and I addressed the crowd.

And I said “I'm glad y'all've got religion; it's my religion, too.
But there's nothing here to see; and I wouldn't lie to you.
It ain't the face of Jesus, and I'll tell you one thing more:
When Jesus comes again it won't be on my kitchen floor.”

But they screamed “Hallelujah, you've got Jesus in the kitchen.”
The mob began to grumble; they were getting kinda wild.
Yelling “Glory Hallelujah, you've got Jesus in the kitchen.”
They were holdin' rakes and kissin' snakes and I thought I might die.

But then a man approached me with a camera in his hand.
He was from the biggest tabloid rag in all the land.
He said he'd pay a thousand bucks to get a photograph
Of the stain that looked like Jesus, and I let go a laugh

And I yelled, “Hallelujah, I've got Jesus in the kitchen.
Everyone can come on in and see my kitchen floor.”
And they all looked and said “This ain't no Jesus in your kitchen.”
They grabbed my little neighbor and they headed for the door.
And he was callin' out for Jesus as they dragged him out the door.

