A Light up in the Sky
by Tim Watson

There's a light up in the sky
There's a light up in the sky
We're all lookin' up and wonderin' why
There's a light up in the sky

They came from far away
So very far away
Some people say they might be here to stay
They came from far away

Wonder what they're doin' here and if they look like us
What are their intentions? Are they honest, are they just?
Will we be their servants, will we be their friends”
Will they show us wonders, or tell us it's the end?

This could be a blessing or a curse
This could be a blessing or a curse
Things just might get better, but they could get a whole lot worse
This could be a blessing or a curse

They say we live in darkness and they're bringing us the light
And we don't know enough to know if that's wrong or right
We've got our suspicions and we're reaching for our guns
But we should be real careful ‘cause there ain't no place to run

There's a light up in the sky
There's a light up in the sky
Don't know if we should laugh or we should cry
Jump for joy or just lay down and die
We're all lookin' up and we're wonderin' why
There's a light up in the sky

Repeat and fade
