Switching Sides
Tim Watson

I see women holding hands with other women
Arms around each other as they stroll
And here I am a man who just can't understand
Why I can't get a girl to have and hold

I've been trying all my life to get a woman
But I've only met with limited success
When they go out with me somehow they come to see
That they like women more and fellows less

So I watch women holding women that I could never get
But it's not completely hopeless.  No, I'm no beaten yet
I see the way to women now, and I'm gonna get me one
I'm gonna get me a sex change, so I can be a lesbian
Lesbian, lesbian – I'm gonna be a lesbian
Yeah I'm gonna get me a sex change and then I can be lesbian

Now some will say that what I plan is cheating
And I confess I'm feeling kinda sly,
It's gender slight-of-hand; inside I'll stay a man
While everyone will think I'm switching sides.

The more I think about it, the more I understand
My destiny has only just begun
I'll still be in the game; the target's just the same
It's only that I'm giving up my gun

These women holding women that I could never get
They'll soon have competition, cause I've got one trick yet
I see the way to women now, and I'm gonna get me one 
I'm gonna get me a sex change, and I can be a lesbian
Lesbian, lesbian – I'm gonna be a lesbian
Yeah I'm gonna get me a sex change and I can be lesbian

And when the doctor's done, then all the world can see
How this hard and lonely life has made a woman out of me
These women loving women, they've been having all the fun
So I'm gonna get me a sex change, and I can be a lesbian
Lesbian, lesbian – I'm gonna be a lesbian
Yeah I'm gonna get me a sex change and I can be a les-bi-an
