Silver Wings (Fly All Night)
by Tim Watson

Staring out a little window, the ground below me drops away
There's a couple holding hands beside me, it takes me back to better days

When you and I were less than married, but something so much more than friends
I'm countin' on these silver wings, to take me back to you again

Chorus
Silver wings, fly all night
Set me down in morning light
She's waiting there for me
Silver Wings.

Second Verse
I'm not a friend of second chances. They never seem to come my way.
But maybe my fortune's changing; I got your message yesterday

And you don't know if we can make it, but you're thinkin' maybe we should try
I'm on my way to you tonight, on this road up in the sky

Chorus
Silver wings, fly all night
Set me down in morning light
She's waiting there for me
Silver Wings.

Bridge
I feel like I'm in the hands of something I can't see
But if it gets me back to you, then that's all right with me.

Third Verse
It seems to me the sky is brighter.  But maybe it's just in my mind.
I've been looking forward for so long, to leaving all these years behind.

Chorus
Silver wings, fly all night
Set me down in morning light
You can leave the rest to me.
Silver Wings.
Silver Wings.
