God Bless Chuck Darwin
Tim Watson

In the 1800's a good man walked the earth
Chuck Darwin was his name, and he was the first
To understand clearly the order of life
But his book led to decades of strife
Decades of anger and decades of strife

A hundred years later they found DNA
In all of God's creatures.  It showed the way
That we are related to all living things
Walkers and swimmers and things that have wings
Crawlers and sliders and all living things

Stop wearing blinders and saying there's a schism
Between God and Darwin, cause there really isn't
Chuck was flesh and blood, with kids and a wife
And he could see so clearly the wonder of life.

In the Good Book, a verse can be found
It says we were made from the dust of the ground
I don't think old Darwin disagreed with that line
He only thought it took a long time
Creation of humankind took a long time

Still so many people, just won't believe.
There are none so blind as those who won't see
How the truth of his teachings set us all free.
“Bang, you are created” just didn't work for me
That old-timey version just wasn't for me.

So stop wearing blinders and saying there's a schism
Between God and Darwin cause you know there isn't
Chuck was a good man who told us the truth.
God bless us all, and Chuck Darwin, too
God bless us every single one… and Chuck Darwin, too

