Makin' This CD
By Tim Watson

First Verse

Oh I lay awake this mornin' wishin' I could just stay there in bed
Cause I knew that I'd end up this way, in this situation that I dread

These double microphones are starin' like a pair of eyes
And I'm about to play a song I wrote and I despise
I'm croakin' like a frog and countin' one, two, three.
Makin' this CD is killin' me.

Second Verse

I ain't lookin' to be famous; I just thought it might be kinda fun
But I'm caught up in a vortex, ain't no place to hide, no place to run

I've been spendin' money that I'll never see again
I think my health is failing in a fight that I can't win
And even as the world grows darker I can finally see
that makin' this CD is killin' me.

Third Verse

It's a world gone crazy, ‘n' I've still got some friends I'd like to get to
But the only ones that I see around me – they're the friends I write the checks to

I guess no one will ever really know the price I've paid
I'll just keep on keepin' on until that final day 
Just three little things keep on getting' in the way – 
I can't write, I can't sing, and I can't play.

Fourth verse

First two lines instrumental

I'd like to breathe some fresher air; I'd like to see the sky
My knees are weak and shakin', and my mouth is feelin' dry
I'm stuck here in this vocal booth and I really need to pee…
Makin' this CD is killin' me.

Makin' this CD is really thrillin'… but it's really killin' me.
